

Rodrigo

Developer



14 July 1983



Monte Alto - SP, Brazil



+55 43 999-108-629



http://goo.gl/F2v0o5



rodfersou@gmail.com

About me –

I am passionate about the art of creating computer programs.

As you can see by looking at my experience, I worry much more about building a solid foundation of knowledge than work just with a particular language. I consider myself able to accept the challenge of working in any environment, language, database or platform.

Skill

Design Patterns

ReactJS

Javascript

Python

CSharp

Delphi

Java

CSS

SOL

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

interests

Good challenges, which demand concentration and focus on quality deliveries.

education

2011-2012 Web Development Specialization course.
Use of offline web pages in the inventory of assets process.

2008-2009 Software Engineering and Database Specialization course.

UEL

2008-2009 Software Engineering and Database Specialization course.

Generating code from a class diagram to an object-relational mapper.

2002-2006 Computer Engineering Graduation.

Adaptive assistant to access classroom tools.

UNOPAR

2000-2001 Data Processing Technical course. CEETEPS

Development of a library management system.

experience

2018-Atual Senior Backend and Frontend Developer Kitconcept GbmH Analysis and development of web portals. (Python / Zope / Plone / ReactJS)

2015-2018 Team leader Simples Consultoria
Analysis and development of web portals. (Python / Zope / Plone)

2014-2015 Software architect

Anicet Corporação

Analysis and development of big data systems and generation of marketing information for e-commerce. (Python / MongoDB)

2012-2014 Developer AVADORA digital Analysis and development of web portals. (Python / Zope / Plone)

2013-2014 Systems Analyst AGILI Softwares para Área Pública Analysis and development of systems and web portals. (CSharp / Oracle)

2011-2012 Senior Systems Analyst MÓDULOS RECAP SOFTWARE LTDA Development and maintenance of ERP for tire retreaders. (Delphi / Firebird)

2011-2011 ABAP Developer PADO SA INDUST. COMERCIAL E IMPORTADORA Customization of SAP ERP screens and reports. (ABAP)

2009-2011 Systems Analyst Maxwell Bohr Instrumentação Eletrônica Development of applications for automation devices. (Python / C / C ++)

2009-2009 Systems Analyst ADVISE DO BRASIL

Development and maintenance of application for automated processing of electronic texts. (Delphi / SQL Server)

2008-2009 Systems Analyst Onixsat Rastreamento de Veículos Ltda
Development and maintenance of GPRS and Satellite messaging server.
(CSharp / SQL Server)

2006-2008 Developer Amcor Flexibles Brasil LTDA Development and maintenance of ERP for flexibles industry.

(Progress 4GL)

2003-2006 Senior Systems Analyst Jabur Informática
Development and maintenance of ERP for vehicle dealers.
(Progress 4GL)

languages

English Understand Well, Speak Well, Read Well, Write Well.

Spanish Understand Well, Speak Reasonably, Read Reasonably, Write Little.

Japanese Understand Reasonably, Speak Little, Read Little, Write Little.